[Music]
[音乐]
one okay Tom time to start
一个好的汤姆时间开始
welcome everyone I hope you are enjoying
欢迎大家，我希望你喜欢
the conference as much as I do
会议和我一样多
my name is Mikkel Babu I work for the
我叫Mikkel Babu，我为
Eclipse Foundation I work in the
我在Eclipse Foundation工作
infrastructure team but I'm I'm also but
基础设施团队，但我也是
from UI committer
从UI提交者
and today I would like to share with you
今天我想和大家分享
some tips and tricks how to debug Java
一些技巧和窍门，如何调试Java
code a bit more effectively so first
首先更有效地编码
thing first I have a short question for
首先，我有一个简短的问题
you what indeed to Sarika talk from
你对Sarika说的确实是什么
yesterday already is the debug
昨天已经是调试了
productive be productive with Java EE
使用Java EE富有成效
okay just a couple of you great because
好的，只是你们几个
they are quite some overlap between the
它们之间有很多重叠
two talks obviously but photos were
显然有两个谈话，但照片是
turned into the tool from yesterday
从昨天变成了工具
hopefully you will get some new tricks
希望你会得到一些新的花样
so second good news oddly no slides
所以第二个好消息奇怪的是没有幻灯片
mostly demos so slightly from it you
大部分是演示，因此略有偏离
will not forget to tell you stuff so the
不会忘记告诉你一些东西，所以
first thing that I would like to share
我想分享的第一件事
with you is how you can customize the
与您一起可以自定义
debug perspective so who are you use the
调试透视图，以便您使用
default layout of the debug capacitive
调试电容的默认布局
so do not touch anything on the layout
所以不要触摸布局上的任何东西
on the debugger okay so will customize
在调试器上可以，因此可以自定义
it really
它真的
wait is that much yeah we'll see if you
等那么多，我们会看看你是否
really customize it the way all the way
完全自定义方式
you can do it so I will show you how I
你可以做到的，所以我会告诉你我
usually do that for myself and maybe you
通常为我自己，也许你
will find it easier so you may you
会发现它更容易，所以您可以
already know that this layout but
已经知道这种布局，但是
especially on this very small screen
特别是在这个很小的屏幕上
very low resolution you are very the
非常低的分辨率，您非常
space to display information so usually
通常显示信息的空间
is the first thing I do is to remove the
我要做的第一件事是删除
outline
大纲
then you change the leader layout which
然后您更改领导者布局
you have the debug besides the editor
您除了编辑器外还有调试
and you have the variables below the
并且您在下面有变量
debug view and also the breakpoints so
调试视图以及断点等
it's a bit easier so to read the code
这样比较容易阅读代码
and we have the variables and debug
我们有变量和调试
stack side-by-side so this is right
并排堆叠，所以这是正确的
quite easy to do but other things you
相当容易做，但是其他事情你
can do is also to customize the menu and
也可以自定义菜单
the cell bar of the debug perspective so
调试透视图的单元格栏
if you right click on the debug
如果您右键单击调试
perspective icon on the top right corner
右上角的透视图图标
you can actually change the toolbar the
您实际上可以更改工具栏
the item visible in the toolbar so
该项目在工具栏中可见，因此
usually when you debug
通常在调试时
don't let the file option talk to the
不要让file选项与
users try stuff you don't need the setup
用户尝试不需要设置的内容
stuff and maybe you don't need the
的东西，也许你不需要
search stuff so if you do that you will
搜索东西，所以如果您这样做
see that your toolbar is already much
看到您的工具栏已经很多
cleaner and you have less stuff to see
更清洁，您所见的东西更少
moving around when you change from one
当你从一个改变时四处走动
perspective to another you can also
透视另一个你也可以
customize a menu so let's say that we
自定义菜单，假设我们
just want the rent menu and the project
只想要租金菜单和项目
menu from air so we can remove
空中菜单，所以我们可以删除
everything except the run and project 1
除了运行和项目1之外的所有内容
and you see also that now the the top
而且您还看到现在顶部
menu are really clean and just have what
菜单真的很干净，只有什么
I need to debug you so this is right
我需要调试你，所以这是正确的
wing but you should change workspaces or
机翼，但您应该更改工作区或
if you by mistake reset your perspective
如果您不小心重设了观点
to zero as it was before you will use
还原为零，然后再使用
this configuration so what you can do is
这种配置，所以您可以做的是
to actually save this debug perspective
实际保存此调试透视图
as your own one so by clicking there so
作为您自己的，所以点击那里
I don't know what to click today I can
我不知道今天可以点击什么
save this configuration on my own
自行保存此配置
perspective and now I'm pretty sure I'm
角度，现在我很确定自己
sure to be able to find it back the
一定能够找到它
exact same way even if I by mistake
完全一样，即使我误会了
visit the diversity to the default still
访问多样性到默认
if you activated the switch to the debug
如果您激活了调试开关
perspective automatically so let's start
自动透视，让我们开始
a debug session just for the
仅用于
cause of the demonstration if i bug this
示范的原因，如果我错误
one the first time you asked you switch
第一次要求您切换
to the debug perspective and usually we
调试角度，通常我们
remember the decision you don't want to
记住你不想做的决定
pop up every time and you're not in your
每次都会弹出，而您不在
own debug perspective you win the
拥有自己的调试视角，您将赢得
default one
默认一个
so changing to the your own customized
因此更改为您自己的自定义
one can be a bit annoying to say so you
一个人可能会有点讨厌，所以你
can change that if you look in the
可以改变它，如果你看着
preferences and search for the
偏好并搜索
perspective in the run debug item you
运行调试项中的透视图
can actually select that when i run a
可以选择当我运行一个
java application with the JIT launcher
JIT启动器的Java应用程序
in the debug mode I want to actually use
在调试模式下，我想实际使用
my own debug perspective and switch to
我自己的调试透视图并切换到
the my own debug perspective and not the
我自己的调试观点，而不是
default one so no if I go back to my
默认一个，所以如果我回到我的我就不
Java perspective and want to debug stuff
Java观点并想调试东西
I automatically switch to my own
我自动切换到自己的
customized one so variant in variable I
自定义变量I的一个so变体
don't know if many of you have to string
不知道你们中的许多人是否必须弦乐
two screens at all but what you can do
共有两个屏幕，但您可以做什么
is also to configure a new perspective
也是配置一个新的视角
to be open in a new window so let me
在新窗口中打开，让我
show you that if I close the perspective
告诉你，如果我关闭透视图
and ask to eclipse to open the when I
并要求日食打开时
open a new perspective I want to open it
打开一个新的视角，我想打开它
in a new window every time then when I
每次当我在新窗口中
start debugging oh of course I get a new
开始调试哦，我当然会得到一个新的
window being open to debug my code so if
窗口打开来调试我的代码，所以如果
you have to screen at home it's really
你必须在家放映
neat you have your work code and the
整洁的你有你的工作代码和
Java perspective on one side on one
Java观点与观点并存
monitor and church you have the debug
监视和教会您有调试
perspective on another window on on the
在另一个窗口上的角度来看
other screen quite a poor
其他屏幕相当差
so this is this a screenshot of some
所以这是一些截图
lanyards that you can do southern point
你可以做南点的挂绳
that I would like to shall we do is
我想做的是
watch points we know what our watch
看点，我们知道我们的手表
points in JIT even those who attended to
JIT中的要点，甚至是那些参加
Sarika talk yesterday come on good
昨天Sarika的谈话很好
question
题
so watch points basically lets you put
所以看点基本上可以让你放
break points when you access or modify a
当您访问或修改
field and lets you put break points when
字段，让您在
you enter a meter or exit a little let
您进入仪表或退出一点
me show you that reading reading I have
我告诉你我正在阅读
some reach there again maybe updating to
一些到达那里可能再次更新为
the latest integration bill yesterday
昨天最新的融合法案
was not really good idea okay so you can
并不是一个好主意，所以你可以
put some bright points on every field
在每个领域上都放一些亮点
modification and field when you read
阅读时的修改和字段
some field values but keep in mind that
一些字段值，但请记住
this has some effect on the performances
这对表演有影响
so if you put some breakpoint on the
因此，如果您在
only field there you can see that the
只有那里，您可以看到
icon is a bit different there are some
图标有些不同
glasses I think you can see that in the
眼镜，我想你可以在眼镜上看到
break point property you can say that
断点属性，你可以说
you want to stop every time you access
您想在每次访问时都停止
the field or modified of it so keep in
字段或对其进行修改，因此请保留在
mind about the performance issue because
考虑性能问题，因为
usually this kind of stuff deactivated
通常这种东西被停用
it and if I'm not mistaking mystical so
它，如果我不误会
this has you stuff remote but can be
这让你的东西很遥远，但可以
quite indeed if you really need to track
确实，如果您真的需要跟踪
this one and another thing is that you
这一件和另一件事是你
can put a breakpoint on a method so by
可以在方法上设置断点，因此
default it's only the entry of the meter
默认情况下，这只是仪表的入口
but in the properties you can also say
但在属性中您也可以说
that you want to stop every time you
你想每次都停止
exit
出口
so let's see how it works if I run that
所以让我们看看如果我运行它是如何工作的
okay let me switch back to the same
好吧，让我切换回原来的状态
window and we'll go back to the default
窗口，我们将返回默认值
just okay I need to cross it from the
好的，我需要从
main window in the same and this one
主窗口与此相同
finale I'm cursed
结局我被诅咒
okay so that nurse at once again
好吧，让护士再次
so you can see that it's a photon
所以你可以看到它是一个光子
integration bill and I get one drop just
整合账单，我得到一滴
to denote update yesterday okay so the
表示昨天可以更新，所以
first check point is not the one I oh
第一个检查点不是我的那个哦
yeah sorry start again no I'm just so
是的，抱歉，再次开始，不，我只是这样
the we have a break point on my field
我们在我的领域有一个转折点
field and you can see that on this line
字段，您可以在这一行看到
the mighty field value is actually
强大的字段值实际上是
written so the debugger is top on the
如此编写，因此调试器位于
modification of the field and if I
修改字段，如果我
continue the next line is actually
继续下一行实际上是
reading the field values so you can see
读取字段值，以便您可以看到
that we are responding while accessing
访问时我们正在响应
this field and if I continue again I'm
这个领域，如果我再继续我
still accessing this field then I'm
仍在访问该字段，那么我
eating the country the fact that I'm
吃这个国家，我是
coming into a mossad so the next watch
进入苔藓，所以接下来的手表
point on the untrained micrometer is
未经训练的千分尺上的点是
triggered and then we are so next is
触发，然后我们接下来
exception break wait
异常中断等待
who knows what is exception records okay
谁知道什么是异常记录可以
so it's quite nd when you want to debug
所以当你想调试的时候
some weird exception that has been
一些奇怪的例外
triggered and you don't know where
触发了，你不知道在哪里
exactly and you want to actually stop on
确切地说，您想停止
any exception being thrown whether you
无论您是否抛出任何异常
cast it or whether it has been untouched
投放或是否未修改
and catched so yeah you have a very
抓住了，是的，你有一个非常
simple code where it will actually throw
简单的代码将实际抛出
a new pointer exception because my field
一个新的指针异常，因为我的领域
is not initialized and then I'm trying
没有初始化，然后我正在尝试
to access to it
访问它
so let's run this thing in debug mode
所以让我们在调试模式下运行
[Music]
[音乐]
set breakpoints yet sorry app so if I
设置断点，但对不起应用程序，所以如果我
want it I get this exception and maybe
想要我得到这个例外，也许
you know maybe you don't know if you
你知道也许你不知道你是否
click on
点击
exception in the consult you actually
实际咨询中的例外
trigger the activation of Java backbone
触发Java主干的激活
exception and you can say whether you
例外，你可以说你是否
want to stop if the exception is only
想停止，如果只有异常
cause or uncocks so let's do that for
原因或un跷，所以让我们这样做
both and if I know start it you can see
两者，如果我知道启动它，您可以看到
that I'm suspended because this line
我被停职，因为这条线
will actually trigger an exception some
实际上会触发一些异常
little option on this on the breakpoint
在断点上的小选择
exception you can actually add them from
您实际上可以从添加它们
this icon in the breakpoint view and for
该图标在断点视图中
instance if you want to stop on all our
如果您想停止我们所有的事
exception you can of course type that
你当然可以输入
but you can also say that you want to
但是你也可以说你想
suspend for all subclasses of this
为此所有子类暂停
exception so this little checkbox can be
例外，所以这个小复选框可以是
easily forgotten sometimes you find a
容易忘记，有时你会发现
bigger key of exception and sometimes
更大的例外关键，有时
you want to stop draw all of them and
你想停止画所有的人
this checkbox will help you do that
此复选框将帮助您做到这一点
okay next conditional breakpoints we
好的下一个条件断点
know what is a conditional breakpoint
知道什么是条件断点
okay
好的
many of you so I will go fast
你们很多，所以我会很快
conditional breakpoints lets you define
条件断点让您定义
a breakpoint that will only stop if one
一个只有在以下情况下才会停止的断点
condition is met so here I have a code
满足条件，所以这里有一个代码
that want to summarize a leaks list of
想要总结泄漏清单
exertional strings so I want you set a
劳累的琴弦，所以我要你设定一个
breakpoint over here and I want to see
在这里的断点，我想看看
what is the value of extreme when it
极端的价值是什么
starts what is the integral integer
开始什么是整数
value of an extreme when it starts with
始于极端的值
let's say thirty two so I'm setting a
假设三十二点，我要设定一个
breakpoint and then going to the
断点，然后转到
breakpoint properties and I'm adding a
断点属性，我要添加一个
condition condition and this condition
条件条件和这个条件
is actually very simple boolean
实际上是非常简单的布尔值
expression that you want to return and
您要返回的表达式，以及
you have access to all the variables
您可以访问所有变量
the from the context so yeah I want to
从上下文出发，是的，我想
check that the strings actually start
检查字符串是否真正开始
with let's say 32 and then if I start
假设32，然后如果我开始
this code in debug mode we will see that
此代码在调试模式下，我们将看到
I am stopping in this code only when my
我只有在我的
string equated with 32 and not in the
字符串等于32，不在
other cases it's radiantly but again it
其他情况下它是发光的，但再次
has some impact on performances so
对表演有一些影响，所以
please don't do that
请不要那样做
in production code only in your own
仅在您自己的生产代码中
development code and one nice thing and
开发代码和一件好事，
one nice improvement from JIT this year
JIT今年的一项不错的改进
that if I continue that if I continue
如果我继续那如果我继续那
the debug session if I step over and
如果我跳过调试会话，
look at the variable view you can see a
看一下变量视图，您可以看到
new item that was not there in the end
最后没有的新物品
so since oxygen you know of the last
所以自从氧气以来，你就知道
value returned by the last mrs. Koll
前夫人返回的值。科尔
always displayed in the variable view so
始终显示在变量视图中，因此
here as we stopped in this method for
在这里，因为我们停止了这种方法
any string starting in 32 I can say that
任何以32开头的字符串我都可以说
this strain has actually been passed as
这种压力实际上已经通过
this integer and it works for any method
这个整数，它适用于任何方法
Collins really really onion lifesaver
柯林斯真的是洋葱救星
it's one reason to move to neon really
这是真正转向霓虹灯的原因之一
next trace point we know what our price
下一个追踪​​点，我们知道我们的价格
points very few so it's it's new in
点很少，所以这是新的
oxygen as well so twice points are
氧气也是两倍
basically conditional breakpoints as
基本有条件的断点为
you've seen in the conditional
你已经在条件
breakpoint you can type any code and you
断点，您可以键入任何代码，然后
can for instance put some system out a
例如可以将某些系统
statement so you can put such a
声明，这样你就可以把
in a condition in the condition and when
在某种情况下
you execute the the con is the the the
您执行的缺点是
code in with the breakpoint you can see
您可以看到带有断点的代码
the the output being written on the
输出写在
console so you don't have to add
控制台，因此您不必添加
anything to your code you just have to
您的代码中的任何内容，您只需要
annotate the breakpoint with some system
用某些系统注释断点
out statements so it's quite handy but
出来的语句，所以很方便，但
pretty unknown so what has been done in
鲜为人知，所以做了什么
oxygen is to add this as as a real
氧气将其添加为真实
breakpoint property so now if you define
断点属性，所以现在如果您定义
if you are online in one twenty find
如果您二十点就上网
some trace point in there you just go to
您只是在其中找到一些跟踪点
the run menu and you ask to toggle
运行菜单，您要求切换
twice point and what it does for you
两次指向，它为您做什么
it's actually just creating a
它实际上只是在创建一个
conditional breakpoint with a default
有默认条件的条件断点
system out and you can of course
系统退出，您当然可以
customize it to output your debug values
自定义它以输出调试值
right in the console so region D
在控制台中，因此区域D
especially when you are debugging
特别是在调试时
remotely some code where you cannot
远程一些您无法执行的代码
modify the out reload the code
修改输出重新加载代码
automatically but still want to print
自动但仍要打印
stuff from the console and really really
来自控制台的东西，真的
trigger points
触发点
who knows what are trigger points okay
谁知道触发点好吗
very few so again it's something new in
很少，这又是新东西
oxygen trigger points breakpoints that
氧气触发点的断点是
will activate other breakpoints so it's
将激活其他断点，因此
easier to see that on an example so
在一个例子中更容易看到
let's say that we have a quick sort
假设我们有一个快速排序
algorithm this kind of algorithm can be
这种算法可以是
quite hard to debug and sometimes you
很难调试，有时您
only want to stop somewhere in the
只想停在
algorithm until some condition has been
算法直到出现某种情况
met or after some code has been executed
满足或执行了一些代码之后
and this is exactly the purpose of a
而这正是
trigger point so let's say that I want
触发点，所以说我想要
to debug this
调试一下
this group yeah the main loop but only
这个小组是主循环，但仅
after the first swap between elements in
在元素之间的第一次交换之后
the array has been executive so I'm
该阵列已经执行，所以我
defining to break point and I will say
定义断点，我会说
that this break point a so the swap will
这个断点一个，所以交换将
be a trigger point
成为触发点
so you either go to the right point
所以你要么去正确的地方
properties activating the trigger point
激活触发点的属性
or you can also do that right from the
或者您也可以直接从
run menu and say that you toggle the
运行菜单，然后说您切换了
know you can do that from the running
知道你可以从跑步中做到这一点
you know you can do that from the break
你知道你可以从休息开始
point view there and says that this one
那里的观点，说这一个
is a trigger point so what it will do it
是一个触发点，那么它将做什么
when I will run the code obviously is
我什么时候运行代码显然是
this break point will be exactly will be
这个断点将是
executed first
首先执行
but the debugger won't stop in there
但是调试器不会在那里停止
because the other one has not been
因为另一个没有
triggered yet so if I run this code with
触发了，所以如果我用
in debug mode can see that I didn't stop
在调试模式下可以看到我没有停止
yet in there any stop here but and the
然而，这里没有任何停靠点，但是
next time I go on there I will stop
下次我继续去那里我会停下来
actually so you can check that by saying
实际上，因此您可以通过说
that group value the rupee telluride not
那组人不喜欢碲化卢比
zero it's not the first time I go inside
零，这不是我第一次进去
my group three out of the six iteration
我的小组六次迭代中的第三次
that I stopped
我停了下来
so it's actually unscoped so it for all
所以实际上它是不受范围限制的
the breakpoints in your that you define
您定义的断点
in your workspaces and what it does is
在您的工作区中，它的作用是
actually deactivate all the break pull
实际上取消了所有的断裂拉力
the trigger breakpoints activate all the
触发断点激活所有
non trigger breakpoints and as soon as
非触发断点，并尽快
one trigger break point has been reached
已达到一个触发断点
it reactivates all the other one correct
它会重新激活所有其他正确的
me if I say yes so the question was is
我如果我说是的话，问题是
it possible to add some condition to a
可能会增加一些条件
trigger breakpoint and yes it is we're
触发断点，是的，我们
at the beginning we know how to remove
一开始我们知道如何删除
the work some java application we've
我们已经完成的一些Java应用程序的工作
changed it's really windy so who has
改变了，真的很刮风，所以谁
already faced this issue where some test
已经面临这个问题，需要一些测试
failed only in the CI environment but
仅在CI环境中失败，但
not on your machine I guess almost
我猜你不在机器上
everyone so how do you divert your CI
大家，所以您如何转移您的CI
environment and because it's only there
环境，因为只有它
that the issue where the issue happens
问题发生的地方
so to that Java is when you well down
所以说Java是当你情绪低落时
and you can actually add an agent to the
您实际上可以将代理添加到
JVM to let you connect to debugger to
JVM让您连接到调试器
remote java java virtual machine so to
远程Java Java虚拟机如此
do that you just have to add this
这样做，您只需要添加此
current line so you will find it on the
当前行，因此您可以在
web pretty easily and yeah i've prepared
网络很容易，是的，我已经准备好了
a very simple application so it's a
一个非常简单的应用程序
string inverter application where you
串逆变器应用在哪里
give a string and interesting about all
给所有的人一个有趣的字符串
the the characters and so this let's say
人物，所以这说
that this application is running on the
该应用程序正在运行
remote server and I will start it with
远程服务器，我将以
the remote debugging mode all so you can
全部使用远程调试模式
see the time I am waiting for a debugger
看到我等待调试器的时间
to actually connect before starting the
在开始之前实际连接
program but I can say also to start the
程序，但我也可以说开始
program and not
程序而不是
wait for the video to connect so that's
等待视频连接，所以
a Java feature and then I go back to my
Java功能，然后回到我的
Eclipse environment and I can define a
Eclipse环境中，我可以定义一个
remote java application they begin
他们开始的远程Java应用程序
configuration so what it says is I want
配置，所以它说的是我想要的
you connect to local host which is those
您连接到 localhost
where the application is running the the
应用程序在哪里运行
port is configuring on the command line
端口在命令行上配置
and I need to say okay this is code
我要说的是，这是代码
actually running on the remote server
实际在远程服务器上运行
the source are in my workspace and I
源在我的工作区中，我
have to give the project name of the of
必须提供的项目名称
the code in my workspace
我的工作区中的代码
so if I run it I didn't define any
所以如果我运行它，我没有定义任何
workplace so you can see that this
工作场所，所以你可以看到
application finished so I will start it
应用程序完成，所以我将启动它
again and in my project now where the
再次，在我的项目中，现在
code of the remote application is
远程应用程序的代码是
located I can put some breakpoint in
定位，我可以在其中添加一些断点
there and if I start again this remote
在那里，如果我再次启动此遥控器
debugging mode so as you can see didn't
调试模式，如您所见
work the reason is there is no scope for
工作的原因是没有范围
trigger points and I still a trigger
触发点，我仍然触发
points and the new run configuration
点和新的运行配置
didn't trigger this trigger point so I
没有触发这个触发点，所以我
have to remove it first and start again
必须先删除它，然后重新开始
the application start again and remove
该应用程序再次启动并删除
the web configuration and now I stopped
Web配置，现在我停止了
into the code of my screening data so
进入我的筛查数据代码
this is really this instance of the of
这确实是
the application that I'm doing with this
我正在做的应用程序
source code so not you it's quite an old
源代码，所以不是你，它是一个很老的
feature but really indeed so breakpoint
功能，但实际上确实如此断点
so again something new in JIT in oxygen
氧气中的JIT又有新内容
you know the default order for sorting
您知道排序的默认顺序
this breakpoints are alphabetically so
这个断点是按字母顺序
it's only when you know in which classes
只有当你知道在哪个班级
you define your breakpoints but usually
您定义断点，但通常
you have to think about okay I want the
你必须考虑好吧，我想要
work through the flow of execution is
通过执行流程进行的工作是
not in the alphabetical order and
不按字母顺序排列
usually you have to find your break
通常你必须找到休息时间
points regarding the flow the execution
关于流程执行的要点
flow of your code and now you can
代码流，现在您可以
actually sort the break points by
实际将中断点排序为
creation time meaning that you will find
创建时间意味着您将发现
at the top
在顶部
the most recent break point you've
您最近的断点
defined and do not have to look at all
定义而不必全看
this code all this list to find the
此代码在所有列表中查找
really proper break point that you want
您想要的真正合适的断点
to deactivate or reactivate so very
非常非常停用或重新激活
handy again this little sought option so
再次方便，这个很少寻求的选择，所以
by default it's still by sub by name but
默认情况下，它仍然按名称命名
you can no stop by creation time don't
您无法在创作时间停下来
group again something new in oxygen so
再次给氧气添加新的东西
who knows what our long troops okay
谁知道我们的长兵还可以
we're sure the user story for that is
我们确定用户故事是
you want to debug some clients and you
你想调试一些客户端，你
need to start a server before being able
需要先启动服务器才能
to debug the client and what you used to
调试客户端以及您以前的操作
do is to okay I want to start the server
可以的，我想启动服务器
you wait for some times so the server
你等了一段时间，所以服务器
actually start okay so now I I know that
实际上开始就好，所以现在我知道了
I can defend my client so it can be
我可以为我的客户辩护
quite repetitive and quite boring so I
非常重复，很无聊，所以我
will stop this one now you with Eclipse
现在您将使用Eclipse停止这一操作
burg you can now create some launch
burg，您现在可以创建一些启动
group launched group are just a group of
团体发起的团体只是一群
one configuration that you've already
您已经拥有的一种配置
defined so it refers to the launch
定义所以它指的是发射
configuration client and server and a
配置客户端和服务器以及
very nice thing is that you can add some
非常高兴的是您可以添加一些
condition after the launch of
发射后的状况
run configuration so yeah I said that
运行配置，是的，我说
after the server has launched do not do
服务器启动后不做
anything wait for a regular expression
任何等待正则表达式的东西
to be output on the console so here if I
要在控制台上输出，所以如果我在这里
don't see several starting on the
没有看到几个开始
console the clients won't start so we've
控制台客户端不会启动，所以我们已经
you have plenty of condition you can
你有很多条件可以
wait for delay or wait until it's
等待延迟或等到
actually terminated but this regular
实际上终止了，但是这个常规
expression stuff is ready and now if i
表情的东西准备好了，现在，如果我
debug this fine this thing you can see
调试这个很好的东西，你可以看到
that the clients actually didn't start
客户实际上没有开始
before the server side that's it was
在服务器端之前
started really poor
开始真的很穷
next is deadlock detection who knows
接下来是死锁检测，谁知道
that jgt can help you detect deadlocks
jgt可以帮助您检测死锁
in your code okay again something new
在您的代码中还可以，有新内容
for you isn't so deadlocks i have
因为你不是那么僵局
created a very simple deadlock code
创建了一个非常简单的死锁代码
example so yeah I have to run able to
例如，是的，我必须能够运行
thread that one is locking block a and
线程锁定块a和
the second one is locking a log B and we
第二个是锁定日志B，我们
try to look in the other order in each
尝试以其他顺序查看
thread so obviously it will create a
线程，因此很明显它将创建一个
deadlock so if I start that right in
僵局，所以如果我从右开始
debug mode or in a Installer mode you
调试模式或在安装程序模式下
will see that nothing nothing is
会看到一无所有
happening but it should finish quickly
发生了，但应该很快完成
because we are just starting to spread
因为我们才刚刚开始传播
and not doing any wait so it's
而且不做任何等待，所以
potentially a deadlock so now I will
潜在的僵局，所以现在我将
debug that and I have a same situation
调试，我有相同的情况
where I see the hostage while running
我在跑步时看到人质的地方
and my main process so let's pose this
和我的主要流程，所以让我们摆姿势
virtual machine and if I post this
虚拟机，如果我发布此
before machine you will see that those
在机器之前，您会看到那些
two thread actually in red and suspended
实际处于红色和暂停状态的两个线程
and you can
你可以
look at which locks they are using and
看看他们正在使用哪些锁，
which locks they are waiting for so you
他们正在等待哪些锁，所以您
can see that this red a is owning the
可以看到这个红色a拥有
object 26 while this red B is actually
对象26而这个红色B实际上是
waiting for this object 26 and this same
等待这个对象26和这个
way around for the object 25 so this is
绕过对象25，所以这是
typically the case for deadlock so you
通常情况下是死锁，所以您
will get an infinite tree between those
那些之间会得到一棵无限的树
two locks so a and E one thing is that
两个锁，所以a和E一件事是
not all JVM supports this kind of
并非所有的JVM都支持这种
deadlock detection because GT is just
死锁检测，因为GT只是
offering some shooting and some UI for
提供一些拍摄和一些用户界面
and what the JVM offers so if you want
以及JVM提供的功能，如果您愿意
to see whether the or JVM support this
查看或JVM是否支持此功能
kind of stuff you can right click on the
您可以右键单击
process in the debug view and look at
调试视图中查看进程并查看
the vm capabilities that you are
您所拥有的虚拟机功能
currently running so here it's a oracle
当前正在运行，所以这里是一个oracle
build of java code and you can have a
Java代码的构建，你可以有一个
look at all the features that it
看一下它的所有功能
supports so for instance the word code
支持，例如单词代码
replace is supported and in the general
支持替换，一般
item you will see whether you support
您将看到您是否支持的项目
the detection or not so if you don't use
检测与否，如果您不使用
come on come on JB and then this view
来吧来吧，然后这个观点
will help you find why you don't see the
将帮助您找到为什么看不到的原因
deadlocks on so next is the inspect and
陷入僵局，接下来是检查和
watch expression but I am running out of
看着表情，但我快用完了
time I would like to go quick to
我想快速去的时间
something even more interesting it's the
更有趣的是
logical structure from jgt so let's say
jgt的逻辑结构，所以说
that we have an interface and user with
我们有一个界面和用户
to implementation optimized users that
实施优化的用户
use a bit set for storing boolean
使用位集来存储布尔值
properties and the hash user would use a
属性和哈希用户将使用
hash map to store the value of the
散列图以存储
problem the properties of the object by
通过以下方式质疑对象的属性
itself if I deeper this is good so I
本身，如果我加深这很好，那么我
have a bunch of users on using the hash
有很多用户在使用哈希
map based and the other
基于地图和其他
optimal when the bit said if I dig this
当我说这个的时候说最好
cold
冷
and look at the variable it can be quite
看一下这个变量
apt you understand - to visualize the
易于理解-可视化
values of the properties because I may
属性值，因为我可能
be not interested into the internal
对内部不感兴趣
structure of the object but only on the
对象的结构，但仅限于
name and the fact that is an employee or
名称和事实，即雇员或
not of the the the real properties of
不属于
the of the object and if I have two
对象的，如果我有两个
different implementation even in
即使在不同的实现
channels are not the same so I we use I
渠道不一样，所以我用我
use the hash map and then we use the we
使用哈希图，然后我们使用
consider boolean the boolean properties
考虑布尔值的布尔属性
she's a bit set and finding something in
她有点固定，在里面找到了东西
a bit set not friendly so something we
有点设置不友好，所以我们
really have for from JDT is to show the
JDT的真正目的是展示
logical structure of an object so
对象的逻辑结构
logical structure will let you define
逻辑结构将让您定义
what are the elements to be shown in the
什么是要显示的元素
variable view for some instances so yeah
某些情况下的可变视图，是的
I define and logical structure for user
我为用户定义和逻辑结构
so on the interface type and as you can
所以在接口类型上
see know either if it's a hash user or
看看是不是哈希用户还是
an optimized user you will always see
您将永远看到的优化用户
the field under the real properties of
真实属性下的字段
the object in the variable view so this
变量视图中的对象，因此
option is not activated by default in
默认情况下，未激活该选项
oxygen used to not be activity by
氧气曾经不被
default and you can define your own
默认，您可以定义自己的
logical structure right from the
逻辑结构从
Preferences if you search for logical
首选项，如果您搜索逻辑
structure and you can do that right from
结构，您可以直接从
here so it's quite simple you just
在这里，这很简单
define the qualified name of the type
定义类型的限定名称
that you on which you want to define the
您要在上面定义的
logical structure and then for each
逻辑结构，然后每个
values you want to display below you
您想在您下方显示的值
define the name of the property and then
定义属性的名称，然后
the code that will be executed so it's
将要执行的代码
quite easy and you can do that right
很容易，你可以做对
from your workspace but then maybe you
从你的工作空间，但也许你
want to do that for your wall team
想要为您的墙队做到这一点
you're not developing your own and you
你不是在发展自己，而你
want to share this kind of announcement
想要分享这种公告
and what you can do is to define
而你能做的就是定义
negative plugin that will provide this
负面插件将提供此功能
logical switch of customization to other
定制向其他逻辑转换
user so for that there is a extension
用户，因此有一个扩展名
point in jgt to define exactly what
在jgt中指向确切定义什么
we've done in the preference page so I
我们已经在偏好页面中完成了，所以我
am defining the logical structure for a
我正在定义一个的逻辑结构
given type for a given type and I'm
给定类型给定类型，我是
giving the name of the attribute I want
给出我想要的属性的名称
to show in the tree and the code that
在树上显示代码
will be executed so if I visited that
将被执行，所以如果我访问了
now you will see that you will be able
现在您将看到您将能够
to debug your code exactly the same way
以完全相同的方式调试代码
with the same logical structure display
具有相同的逻辑结构显示
in full bundled Eclipse without having
在完全捆绑的Eclipse中，而无需
to go to the Preferences and redo that
去首选项并重做
again and again so if I now go to the
一次又一次，所以如果我现在去
preferences and sahaja Cal structure I
偏好与哈嘉Cal结构I
will see that the same thing is defined
会看到定义了相同的内容
but if I look at the details there it
但是如果我看那里的细节
has been contributed from an extension
由扩展贡献
point and I cannot actually edit or
点，我实际上无法编辑或
remove it because it has been defined in
删除它，因为它已经在
a plug-in that I've deployed in inside
我已经部署在内部的插件
my Eclipse we have any question and may
我的Eclipse，我们有任何问题，可能
have time for one question
有时间提出一个问题
okay so what you should remember about
好吧，那你应该记住什么
these tips and tricks list today
这些提示和技巧今天列出
so JDT is really awesome - it provides a
所以JDT真的很棒-它提供了一个
lot of helpful menus and items to help
很多有用的菜单和项目，以帮助
you debug more easily and to be more
您可以更轻松地调试，并且变得更好
proactive so to discover all of this I
积极主动，以便发现所有这一切
can encourage you to browse the
可以鼓励您浏览
Preferences of the debug agenda by
调试议程的首选项
traveling at the menu and of course to
在菜单上旅行，当然
read the dark because almost everything
阅读黑暗，因为几乎所有东西
I showed you today it's already in the
我今天告诉你，它已经在
help menu of Eclipse so you could have
Eclipse的帮助菜单，因此您可以
discovered that by yourself
自己发现了
thank you very much and if you have more
非常感谢你，如果你还有更多
question maybe other
问题也许其他
[Applause]
[掌声]